{
    "subject": "resource/Prince_of_Persia:_The_Sands_of_Time",
    "predicate": "property/publisher",
    "object": "*Gameloft",
    "human_readable": "Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time was published by Gameloft.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9602768421173096,
            "question": "Who published Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8303053975105286,
            "question": "When was Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7268937230110168,
            "question": "What genre is Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7125348448753357,
            "question": "Which game was published by Gameloft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047862410545349,
            "question": "What is the main character's name in Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7041907906532288,
            "question": "What are some popular features of Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6670308709144592,
            "question": "What company released Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5111123919487,
            "question": "Are there other games published by Gameloft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40944990515708923,
            "question": "Is Gameloft a video game publisher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0943032056093216,
            "question": "What is the name of the game publisher?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time was published by Gameloft.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1950_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Gameloft a video game publisher?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1950_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other games published by Gameloft?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1950_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company released Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1950_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1950_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, \"Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time\" was published by Ubisoft, not Gameloft. This can be confirmed from documents like `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1950/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1950/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt`, which state that it was published by Ubisoft."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}